here we are back on hermitcraft now
something happened
off-camera between episodes and I kind
of got to tell you about because it
resulted in me getting 10 blocks of
diamonds that's right what happened was
that I was over here just helping out
Wren dog now he was working on his bass
and he was having a bit of a hard time
while streaming so I came over here and
I was helping him build and then I
realized as I started to look more
closely at his circle the hid made more
than one mistake and then I asked him
Wren
hey Ren is this a true circle and he was
like he was like no so I basically spent
a couple of hours with him and I plotted
out a perfect circle over the top of his
and I even marked out where his pillars
should be and in return I got 10 diamond
blocks okay being a good friend and
getting diamond blocks that's a win-win
but what are we going to do in today's
episode well well well well I'm going
the wrong direction really really big
things are about to happen this big
thing I'm going to make the biggest the
bestest minecraft mansion expansion you
have ever seen so at the moment we've
got the G mansion there it is the little
G up there and it's looking pretty cool
but every time I look at this build
there's just dead space all around here
and all around here so what we're going
to do today or we're going to attempt to
do is an enormous expansion of it I
won't get everything done as I normally
don't because you know time this all
takes time but we are going to do our
best to make this mansion one of the
best builds on the hermit craft server
but first we need to head over to a leg
room bot because mumbo and I need to
know what we do now we've already got
our Mambo from their t-shirts link
the description but we need to know what
to do next so I'm heading over to
Grumbach right now oh my goodness look
at this Joe Joe Joe has a lot of support
for becoming dog catcher oh wow
Oh stress is I think in the lead in the
mayoral race scar trailing that little
bit oh god I can't believe we managed to
get him to do that right let's head over
oh wait a second I thought something was
missing
look at this someone won I assume tagged
to electric boogaloo hold on
yep I just asked the group Corrales and
Exuma have won the tag game it's about
time really tag to electric boogaloo
finally over I don't really know what
happened but I'm kind of glad that it's
over we can get rid of this eyesore in
the shopping district don't be done with
it there we go all cleared up now this
is actually a prime piece of real estate
and I think I want to buy more land next
to the barge just in case of an
expansion so these 10 diamond blocks
that I just got from rent right we're
gonna buy loads of land one two three
four five I'm adding to the diamond
throne nine ten there we go
I get ten bits of land this is this is
what distractions look like mumbos now
waiting for me over by the Grumbach okay
let's go it's a nice t-shirt number why
thank you do you like how I've it's
still I had to maintain the height of
the trousers you look like the worst
superhero well you know what's funny
though is that is a little bit
embarrassing because I look like I've
just got a t-shirt with my name on it my
diamond pile is a tiny bit embarrassing
as well you know yeah grandpa asked for
budget I thought oh yeah I was like you
know this is decent amount what's that
yeah five well grandpa doesn't seem to
be too upset so I think no no no that
it's slide I still don't know what he
wants these diamonds for which is know
kind of why we're here what does he want
now we're both wearing our Mambo from
their tea
shirts and yeah looking good shameless
plug link is in the description for
those of course of course and I can't
even see yours cuz you what do we ask
him now
um I mean do you have any ideas alright
you called me over here right grumble
tell us what to do it's not even a
question just tell us what's a command
to do okay all right let's prime him up
prime grub bootloader brain flood those
mayoral reservoirs yep and go ok I'm
nervous why am I not there we go what is
he ok
what is he saying you're saying
processing oh oh wait wait I guess yeah
I mean the paper just says processing
and that's it right what does he say so
he was just kind of working things out
ok readout in Croatian well I want you
to do an impression of Grandpa
oh my goodness what would grumbles sound
like he PBB you know what I'm gonna give
this to you you know what voice would
you give it now no now he put me on the
spot don't ask arias instructions for my
creator because he types a types in
capital letter he doesn't do that ok
fine keep that going create a one build
a grumble shop creator to build a
minecraft film studio I love how he
specified a minecraft one just just in
case you were gonna go out to the real
world excuse oh great yeah um he's
giving us both instructions oh so
there's nothing more than that no that's
it that's it I guess we need to decide
who's creative one who's creative two
now well I mean I just want to say I
think I'd like to take the task of
building a film studio that sounds like
fun
ok ok I don't know what what is a
Grumbach shop
you don't know what's the fam why do I
need to build it films for a second
question what any of this means
it is totally expression there's a
hundred yards there yeah okay well um is
that it should we ask him is there any
is there anything else grumble really
yep you can do it can miss the first one
my first first one you can you can do
this one alright can you elaborate so we
need to prime we need to boot loads I
need to flood the cut out mustache on
the back of your head that has been the
the centerpiece of all my thumbnails
recently it's like the main thing they
shoot this thing through right so
hopefully he elaborates crumble
elaborate explain yourself oh well he's
emotionless again not really always
given to he's given to what mundo Khmer
goodness why do we build this blindly
give him loads of diamonds and do you
know he's intentionally vague so we keep
asking him more and he gives more
diamonds that is a pro-level move to be
honest with you yeah maybe I might have
made like a diamond hungry robot he just
gives just a little bit too little
information asking him all right well I
guess we don't question this I'm gonna
go and build a Grumbach shop whatever
that is and you need to ya know studio
some for some reason okay well he's
playin dude yeah what on earth is a
Graham bot shop I think I've got a good
idea but I'm not sure if it's gonna work
take a good look at grumble himself
because I think a grumble shop should
just be a smaller cuter version of him I
have no idea what it even sells
it does say grumble shop right yep build
a grumble shop so I just message mumbo
and he said we can actually use this
plot over here where he sold his bits
cuz he no longer needs it so we've
already got a really nice little space
here for us to use but before we get
into that build I want to check on the
barge because I've been told yes again
that I'm running out of stock oh my
goodness not even a little bit I'm just
gonna I'm gonna scoop up all the money
oh we sold some maps and item frames
making some sales oh my goodness we have
sold so many look at that look at that
three and a half stacks of diamonds from
the barge in the last few days I think
we're doing upgrade but I'm not sure we
have time because we need to go and make
this grumble Junior and that means sorry
how did you get here you're nuts you're
not safe no no no I'm not what do I do
okay can I kill it there we go I'll just
I'll just pop you in there what the his
helmet just broke I'll save you though
I'll save you
he's gonna go anyway let's get clearing
this thing so I'm thinking what we need
to make here is like I said grumble
Junior a smaller version that sells
pleure I don't know what it sells
because brahmbhatt hasn't given us any
information whatsoever here's my plan
here's my plan we make the cutest shop
ever that no one can ignore that's the
plan and then when whenever we find out
what it sells we can adapt it fairly
easily alright so with that in mind
let's get started and do a quick time
lapse of Grumbach I don't like the name
Grumbach Junior well I'll come up with a
name I'll come up with a name while I'm
building it I think that's probably for
the best
[Music]
I think we just won the competition for
the cutest shop that has ever existed
and I've got a brand new name for this
guy
this is grumbles little brother drum bot
now since I have no idea what Graham bot
wants us to sell in here I've left it
blank for now so I'm actually gonna
cover up the entrance and just leave it
here cuz I have no idea what this is for
but oh my goodness isn't this a we can
make it even cuter as well you would
have thought that drew drum I can't say
it drum bot wears sandals
it wears little sandals oh it makes them
even more to you oh and and and it
doesn't end there who would have thought
but Graham BOTS little brother was a
blusher oh it's adorable
everyone everyone is gonna want to shop
here whatever it sells everyone is going
to want to shop here look at his little
antenna it's got a blue ball instead of
a red one isn't that just precious look
at his little sandals I've given him
little arms because I figure whatever he
ends up selling he can just hold in his
hands but don't you just want to give
this little guy hug oh it's so cute all
right okay we're done here we've we've
done what Graham bot has asked we'll
meet up with mumbo when he's ready and
we'll ask
Grum bot - what what on earth we do next
I have no idea what mumbo has done in
terms of his film studio but I am really
excited to show him this Hey
it's just so cute however it is now time
to head back to the base I'd love to
keep working on this but I think I've
just achieved perfection here we've got
a lot of work to do that bill didn't
take nearly as long as the one we're
about to do as I said at the beginning
of the episode what I plan to do is the
great mansion
expansion which is build it out and down
and out and down and out and down and
what we'll end up with is a enormous
semicircle and it will have a plaza in
the middle this is going to be the
single biggest addition to this build
since we started it and it will finally
start to look a little bit more complete
however I can't just start building it
because I have no resources for a
project like this man these are the bits
that you don't really appreciate it's
very easy to think about just going
straight into the build but you've got
to prepare beforehand so I've got to get
all my shoulder boxes ready let's go I
mean this is this is the worst part of
the job just collecting the materials
[Music]
I need a more tired looking face on my
skin because that was exhausting
I barely have time to build my actual
base now because I spent my entire day
gathering these resources now this
probably isn't enough but who really
knows it's just it's just ludicrous why
did I build an item sorter when it all
ends up outside anyway either way it's
time to get started on the reason we're
all here the mansion expansion so we've
got a time-lapse to do and some elbow
grease to release and the Sun is setting
is probably a really bad time to start
eye maps but let's get going
[Music]
well there we go check it out we've
actually got some chimneys on our
mansion we have extended it and made it
blend more and more into the ground oh
my goodness there's a block missing I'll
tell you what the worst thing is about
this base is you're in the time lapse
you'll see me jump down jump up jump
down jump up it's because there is so
many different kinds of blocks and
there's not enough space in the
inventory you know now I'm here I can't
actually see we're missing block is
there it is there it is it's very easy
to miss a block on something like this
and I gotta say a huge thank you to
pearlescent moon who in during my two
days and it was two full days on my
private server trying to figure out the
design of this I got like I got this I
got like the semicircle shape like all
the details and the chimneys and
everything and I was just struggling to
detail these large walls and pearlescent
moon help me out with these these bits
here that you see that jut out
absolutely perfect so she kind of saved
me there cuz I was I was hitting a bit
of a block so a huge thank you again to
pleasant moon for the design help but
what do you think of that obviously I
want to make the same thing on the other
side and I was planning to before I
realized actually that's a huge amount
of blocks a really really large amount
of blocks and the worst pay is I'm dead
I'm dead broke nothing left not a single
diamond to my name and I had a lot I had
a decent amount of diamonds but I spent
it all on this dark Prisma reed I mean
we're talking stacks of diamonds to get
enough for this build so I've actually
stopped I'm scared I won't be able to
complete the other side so I think for
next episode I'm planning to have the
full mansion expansion including the
work on the back I've actually filled in
the back of this bit as you can see here
there's not detailed but it's filled in
and then next episode I'm hoping I can
get more and more done I always seem to
bite off more than I can chew and it's
not a good thing to do
I start off the episode saying yeah I'm
gonna build this whole thing in one go
and then I actually get here and this
episode is already extremely late so
here we are next episode I'm hoping to
replicate it over and add even more to
this build I think this looks absolutely
fantastic it's worth mentioning that I
will do something about all the snow
because on my creative world there is no
snow on the build and it looks so much
more clean and that means string I need
a lot of string and a lot of patience to
fix all of this stuff but I'm afraid
that is all we have time for today look
at that so much progress such an amazing
build that's happening here so with that
I say thank you very much for watching
three time lapses and a grumble session
what an episode and I shall see you in
the next one thanks again for watching
and good bye remember you can get Mambo
from their t-shirts in the description
and also if you want to see Mambo just
Chiang nonsense just wait a second
though they'll leave a clip at the end
rumba is reaching further into the earth
I don't know how we would how would he
operate the earth I don't know where I'm
going with this you know any sentence
than halfway through